A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Grants, RG 5 FA1403
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Theater, 1964-2006; 19; 34.53 Cubic Feet 84 letter document boxes and 2 record storage boxes
  - Philippines, 19.14
    - Yoo, Janice and Duk-Hyung, Philippine Education Theater Association (PETA) Training Consultants, B-7256, DF-7287, 1972 (Box 924, Folder 6)
    - Philippine Education Theater Association (PETA), B-7640-AIP, 1976 (Box 925, Folder 1)
    - Cunada, Isabel, Dallas Theater Center, B-6821, B-6876, DF-69108, DF-7076, 1968-1970 (Box 925, Folder 2)
    - Duque, Felix S., East-West Center-University of Hawaii, B-7333, DF-7378, 1973 (Box 925, Folder 3)
    - Guidote, Cecile, B-6526, DF-6506, DF-6753, DF-6754, DF-6760, 1965-1967 (Box 925, Folder 4)
    - Guidote, Cecile, B-6526, DF-6506, DF-6753, DF-6754, DF-6760, 1967 (Box 925, Folder 5)
    - Guidote, Cecile, Ramavana Festival, B-6526, DF-6506, DF-6753, DF-6754, DF-6760, 1965-1967 (Box 925, Folder 6)
    - Guidote, Cecile, International Theater Institute (ITI), US Travel, DF-6753, 1967 (Box 925, Folder 7)
    - P.E.T.A.-ITI, Theater Specialist, Brook Jones, B-7145, DF-7182, 1971 (Box 926, Folder 1)
    - Third World Theater Festival-Conference, PETA and IT, Manila, B-7270, DF-7283, 1971 November 19-30 (Box 926, Folder 2)
    - Catoy, Virgilio San Juan, DF-7766, 1977 (Box 926, Folder 3)
    - Mendoza, Maria Liwayway Gamboa, DF-7770, DF-7857 (, 1977-1978 (Box 926, Folder 4)
    - Jones, Brooks, DF-8794, 1987 (Box 926, Folder 5)
    - Labad, Lutgardo, B-7543, 1975 (Box 926, Folder 6)
    - Population Communication International, DF-9227, 1992 (Box 926, Folder 7)
    - San Francisco Mime Troupe, DF-9191, 1991 (Box 926, Folder 8)
    - Gonzales, Gino, 100-00-20048.1, 100-00-990404.1, 100-00-98042.1, 1998-2000 (Box 926, Folder 9)
    - Asia Society, 100-00-20011-203.2, 2000 (Box 927, Folder 1)
    - Bharucha, Rustom, 100-00-20129-203.3, 2000 (Box 927, Folder 2)
    - Juan, Anton, 100-00-94003-203.000-3, 1994 (Box 927, Folder 3)
    - Ma-Yi Theatre Ensemble, 100-00-99049-203.000-1, 1999 (Box 927, Folder 4)
    - Ma-Yi Theatre Ensemble, 100-00-98009-203.1, 1998 (Box 927, Folder 5)
    - New York Shakespeare Festival, 100-00-20161-203.3, 2000 (Box 927, Folder 6)
    - University of Hawaii at Manoa, 702-00-99017-203.2, 1999 (Box 928, Folder 1)
    - Cultural Center of the Philippines, 655-00-24101-203.1, 2004 (Box 928, Folder 2)
    - Francia, Luis, 655-00-23095-203.1, 2003 (Box 928, Folder 3)
    - Infante, Emilio, 578-00-99097-203.1, 100-00-20032-203.3, 1999 (Box 928, Folder 4)
    - Ma-Yi Theatre Company, 655-00-23027-203.2, 2003 (Box 928, Folder 5)
    - Tan-Tiongco, Mareee Barbara, 639-00-22076-203.2, 2002 (Box 928, Folder 6)
    - Women Playwrights International, 655-00-23099-203.1, 2003 (Box 928, Folder 7)
    - Women Playwrights International, 655-00-23099-203.1, 2003 (Box 929, Folder 1)
  - Singapore, 19.15
    - Tang, Fu Kuen, 100-00-21063-203.1, 2001 (Box 929, Folder 2)
    - Theatreworks, 100-00-98045-203.1, 1998 (Box 929, Folder 3)
    - Yo, Shaoann, 100-00-21064-203.1, 2001 (Box 929, Folder 4)
    - Ong, Keng Sen, 100-00-94028-203.000-1, B-9323, 1993-1994 (Box 929, Folder 5)
    - Practice Performing Arts School, 100-00-21069-203.1, 2001 (Box 930, Folder 1)
  - Sri Lanka, 19.16
    - Gunawardana, A. J., B-6710, EC-6903, 1967. 1969 (Box 930, Folder 2)
    - Lionel Wendt Memorial Fund, B-7057, 1970 (Box 930, Folder 3)
    - Sarachchandra, Ediriweera R., B-6711, 1967 (Box 930, Folder 4)
    - Tilakisiri, J., DF-8898, 1988 (Box 930, Folder 5)
  - Taiwan, 19.17
    - Chinese Culture Foundation of San Francisco, Chang Te-Chen Shadow Play Troupe), B-7352, 1973 (Box 930, Folder 6)
    - Hung, Josephine Huang, B-6508, 1965 (Box 930, Folder 7)
    - Change, Ivy, 702-00-96055-203.000-1, 702-00-95051-203.000-1, 1995-1996 (Box 931, Folder 1)
    - Chung, Mingder, B-9125, 1991 (Box 931, Folder 2)
    - Hsu, Jui-Fang, 100-00-96003-203.000-3, 1996 (Box 931, Folder 3)
    - Friedman, Steve, 100-00-97142-203.3, 1997 (Box 931, Folder 4)
    - Peet, Yin and Uchida, Bart-HWA Deng Theater Group, 494-00-96044-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 932, Folder 1)
    - Schechner, Richard, 479-00-95041-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 932, Folder 2)
    - Silvio, Teri J., 706-00-96069-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 932, Folder 3)
    - Chi-Body Theatre Troupe, 100-00-22136-203.1, 2002 (Box 932, Folder 4-5)
    - La MaMa, E.T.C., 100-00-98008-203.2, 1998 (Box 932, Folder 6)
    - Liu, Mei Yin, 100-00-96035-203.000-1, 100-00-97024-203.000-2, 1996-1997 (Box 933, Folder 1)
    - Schechner, Richard, 100-00-24028-203.3, 2004 (Box 933, Folder 2)
  - Thailand, 19.18
    - Grow, Mary, 706-00-96070-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 933, Folder 3)
    - Grow, Mary, B-8696(56)R, 1986 (Box 933, Folder 4)
    - International WOW Company, 634-00-22119-203.1, 2002 (Box 933, Folder 5)
    - Kwong, Dan, 100-00-20063-203.1, 2000 (Box 933, Folder 6)
    - Na-Pombejra, Dangkamon, 100-00-20050.1, 100-00-99041.1, 1999 (Box 933, Folder 7)
    - Mahasarinand, Pawit, 100-00-20132.3, 100-00-98027.3, 100-00-20006.3, 100-00-95030.1, 1998-2000 (Box 934, Folder 1-2)
    - Makhampom Theatre Group, 718-00-25018-203.2, 2005 (Box 934, Folder 3-4)
    - Prasartthong, Pradit, 634-00-23088-203.1, 2003 (Box 935, Folder 1)
    - Swasdiprom, Nutjapotn, 742-00-25106-203.1, 718-00-25107-203.1, 2005 (Box 935, Folder 2)
    - Thammapruksa, Narumol, 100-00-98043-203.1, 1998 (Box 935, Folder 3-4)
  - Vietnam, 19.19
    - Asia Society, B-9237, 1992 (Box 936, Folder 1)
    - Bird, Tom, DF-8414, 1984 (Box 936, Folder 2)
    - La MaMa, E.T.C., Vietnam National Theater, 494-00-96045-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 936, Folder 3)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, 100-00-96008-203.2, 1996 (Box 936, Folder 4)
    - Movement Theater International, DF-9216, 1992 (Box 936, Folder 5)
    - Viet Nam Generation, 100-00-95034-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 936, Folder 6)
    - Hoang, To Mai, 100-00-96098-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 937, Folder 1)
    - Nguyen, Thi Minh Ngoc, 634-00-23089-203.1, 2003 (Box 937, Folder 2-3)
    - Gray, Spalding, DF-8413, 1984 (Box 937, Folder 4)
- Memorabilia, 20; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
  - Seoul Institute of The Arts (gold medal in blue velour box) (Box 7A)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted from research due to preservation concerns.
  - The Philippine Educational Theater Association Presents a Plaque of Appreciation to Mr. Porter McGray (PETA) (boxed with note) (Box 7A)
  - Jaya Raya, Metal and Plaque and explanation of the Coat of Arms from Jakarta (Red box) (Box 7A)
  - Post cards, pictures and phone book with a hole burned in the center (blue wooden box) (Box 7A)
- ACC Audio, 1956-1990; 21; 1.41 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes and 1 phono box
  Open for research. When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  Sound recordings
  - Autonomy of Voice, music composed by Shuko Mizuno, 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Reel AV 9936)
    Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Jawn Tinqal, 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Reel AV 9937)
  - Musik Jakapt, 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Reel AV 9938)
  - General Culture-Indonesia, Ismail, Taufiq (Mr.), circa 1970s; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Reel AV 9939)
  - The Crucible - LPKJ, Kemelut Oleh Mahasiswa Theater, 1975 June 25; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Reel AV 9940)
  - Music-China - Ni, Wen-Zhen (Mr.), B-8571, 1985; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9941)
  - Gathutkaca Sungging (Gathut Kaca Restored), Dhalang: Ki Nartasabda from Semarang, Lokananta, Cassette ACD-022, Sides 8 and 9, Representing One-Eighth of the Performance, (Audio and Translation), 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9942)
  - Wayaug Mircum, AMU, PRM, Ande-Ande Lumut, Lokananta Recording, 1975 November 17; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9943)
  - Wayaug Mircum, AMU, PRM, Klenengan Among Karsa, Lokananta Recording: Pangkur, 1975 November 17; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9944)
  - Wayaug Mircum, AMU, PRM, ?Klenengan?, Lokananta Recording: Rangu-Rangu, 1975 November 17; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9945)
  - Music-Pakistan - Husain, Imdad - Tape 1, B-7645, DF-7668, Grant Related, 1976; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9946)
  - Music-Pakistan - Husain, Imdad - Tape 2, B-7645, DF-7668, Grant Related, 1976; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9947)
  - Music-Pakistan - Husain, Imdad - Tape 3, B-7645, DF-7668, Grant Related, 1976; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9948)
  - Music-Pakistan - Husain, Imdad - Tape 4, B-7645, DF-7668, Grant Related, 1976; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9949)
  - Music-Pakistan - Husain, Imdad - Tape 5, B-7645, DF-7668, Grant Related, 1976; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9950)
  - Paik, Eui-Hyun - Music/Korea: "Symphony Orchestra" - Indiana University School of Music, 1978 November 1; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Reel AV 16038)
    Scope and Contents
    Eui Paik's Symphony No. 1 - Andante and Allegro (1977). World Premiere Performance. Katsuhiko Watanabe, Conductor. "Dedicated to the John D. Rockefeller III Foundation"
  - Music-Japan - Nakamura, Hiroko, B-6614, 1966; Plastic sound disc: LP (Box 2, Disc AV 6021)
    General
    Four 9 inch flexible sound discs with hardcover book: Beethoven
  - Toru Takemistu, Stanza No. 1, Sacrifice Ring Valeria, Vinyl sound disc: LP (Box 2, Disc AV 6008)
  - Three Japanese Poets: Ryuichi, Tamura. Shuntaro Tanikawa. Yuzuru Katagiri, 1971; Vinyl sound disc: LP (Box 2, Disc AV 6009)
  - Side 1-Raga Bhorirobi, Bilambit Thintal. Side 2-Raga Iman, Rupaktal, Drut Thintal, and Jahala, 1970 September 16; Acetate sound disc: LP (Box 2, Disc AV 6010)
    Sitar: Peter Row; Tabla: Govinda Bose; Tampura: Kalpana Row
  - Paper Drums, Shoichi, Ida, 1986; Plastic(?) sound disc (Box 2, Disc AV 6011)
  - Catch Wave: Takehisa Kosugi, 1974; Vinyl sound disc: LP (Box 2, Disc AV 6012)
    CBS/Sony Inc. SOCM 88
  - Senno Ongaku by Jo Kondo, circa 1970-1990; Vinyl sound disc: LP (Box 2, Disc AV 6013)
    ALM Records
  - Kasilag: East-West - CCP Philarmonic Orchestra, Zenas Reyes-Lozada, Soloist, 1975; Vinyl sound disc: LP (Box 2, Disc AV 6014)
  - Jo Kondo: Mr. Bloomfield, His Spacing, 1970-1976; Vinyl sound disc: LP (Box 2, Disc AV 6015)
    ALM RecordS, AL-13(A) and AL-13(B)
  - Hijikata, Tatsumi, circa 1970s-1980s; Vinyl sound disc: LP (Box 2, Disc AV 6016)
  - Experimental Music of Japan, Mayuzumi and Moroi, Takemistu, Yuasa, Mayuzumi, Ichiyanagi. Ishii, 1956-1967; Vinyl sound disc: LP (Box 2, Disc AV 6017)
    Victor Records, SJV-1515
  - The Experimental Theatre Company of La MaMa-New York presents Carmilia, A Vampire Tale (Off-Broadway recording with original cast), 1972; Vinyl sound disc: LP (Box 2, Disc AV 6018)
    Music by Ben Johnston. Script by Wilford Leach. Vanguard Records, VSD-79322
  - Suasana Teater Ensemble: Jentaya, 1982; Vinyl sound disc: LP (Box 2, Disc AV 6019)
  - Contemporary Clarinet: F. Gerard Errante, 1987-1988; Vinyl sound disc: LP (Box 2, Disc AV 6020)
    Capstone Records, CPS-8604
  - Printed material associated with audio items (Box 949, Folder 8-10)